Guide to the ILGWU. Sol Chaikin papers,
ILGWU. Sol Chaikin papers,
- Series VIII. Correspondence, 1953-1991
  - Open Society, Fund For An, 1976-1986 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    (Chaikin, Member, Board of Directors) Information booklet and related routine.
  - Organization for Rehabilitation Through Training, 1975-1984 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    (Chaikin, Member, Board of Directors) Re ORT celebration of 100th Anniversary; meetings and activities.
  - Organizations. Committees, 1976-1980 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    Releases of American Committee for Protection of Foreign Born; invitations to serve on committees and for speaking engagements from Committee for U.N. Integrity, A Presidential Classroom for Young Americans, Association of Community College Trustees, White House Conference on Families, Citizens' Library Council of NYS, Citizens Action on Crime, Committee of New Yorkers for July 4th, International Hapoel Games, Project HOPE, and others.
  - Organizations. Honors, 1976-1980 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    Invitations from groups and organizations to sponsor or attend dinners honoring individuals.
  - Organizations. Invitations, 1976-1979 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    Invited to serve as charter member of North-South Round Table, as Honorary Member of Brooklyn Bicentennial Commission, Freedom Monument Committee and others.
  - Organized Crime Strike Force, 1977-1978 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    Re matter of Interstate Dress Carrier and Local 102 concerning organizing tactics, financial and legal problems.
  - Organizing Committee for a New Jewish Agenda, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Outerwear, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    50 p. "Study of Collective Agreements in the Coat and Suit, Dress and Skirt and Sportswear Industry.."
  - Overseas Development Council, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Overseas Private Investment Corporation, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    Re AFL-CIO opposing OPIC.
  - Overseas Unions, 1975-1985 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    Includes 7 p., "Imprisoned Workers and Unofficial Trade Unionists in the USSR," by Amnesty International; "Public Statements" of Trade Union Congress of the Philippines; National Union of Clothing Workers (South Africa) re clothing industry and other issues; Garment Workers Union of South Africa re inflation; Chinese Federation of Labour; Federation of Korean Trade Unions; Hungarian Trade Unions; and others.
  - Parsons School of Design, 1981-1986 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    Re preparations for awards show and dinner.
  - Paturis, Cleo, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Peabody, Endicott, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    Re political support.
  - Pechner, Dorfman, Wolffe, Rounick and Cabot, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    Re Chaikin guest speaker at 5th Annual Labor Relations Update Seminar, includes 52 p. booklet.
  - Pennsylvania Crime Commission, 1983-1985 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    Re preliminary investigation into the ladies garment manufacturing industry.
  - Pennsylvania Junior College of Medical Arts, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - People for the American Way, 1981-1985 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    Correspondence re financial support, meetings, etc.
  - Personal Sportswear [folder 1 of 2], 1982-1985 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    Includes financial documents and copies of supplemental agreements re Leslie Fay Co., Personal Sportswear Division.
  - Personal Sportswear [folder 2 of 2], 1982-1985 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Personnel Review Committee, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    Re decisions on wage and per diem policy.
  - Peru, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    Information, correspondence, and notes re Chaikin's attendance at the IV Western Hemisphere Labor Economics Conference in Lima; 4 p. re "Political Situation."
  - Phelps Dodge, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    Re support for Phelps Dodge strikers.
  - Phillips Center for Public Research, 1982-1985 (Box 37, Folder 28)
    Re operational structure of the Center; copy of a letter from an anti-union consultant who was an organizer for 20 years.
  - Piece Rate Committee, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 29)
    Staff suggestions and views re piece rates; reports, recommendations and statistical information.
  - Pierce, Barbara, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Plant Closing Legislation, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 31)
    Re NYS legislation. request for ILG to participate in hearings.
  - Poland, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 32)
    Letter from Chaikin to Lech Walesa re American support; financial support to aid Polish workers.
  - Policy Project, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - Political Campaigns [folder 1 of 2], 1981-1984 (Box 37, Folder 34)
    Correspondence with Senator Edward Kennedy, Joseph Biden, Tip O'Neill, and others; Political Campaign Committee financial report; authorizations to districts and locals for contributions to political candidates; form letters and lists.
  - Political Campaigns [folder 2 of 2], 1981-1984 (Box 37, Folder 34a)
  - Political Contributions, 1975-1980 (Box 37, Folder 35)
    Related routine correspondence re contributions.
  - Political Contributions [folder 1 of 2], 1983 (Box 37, Folder 36)
    Thank you letters from politicians for the generous support of the ILGWU.
  - Political Contributions [folder 2 of 2], 1983 (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - Political Contributions [folder 1 of 2], 1984-1986 (Box 37, Folder 38)
    Same as above.
  - Political Contributions [folder 2 of 2], 1984-1986 (Box 37, Folder 39)
  - Politics, 1971-1976 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    3 p. summary of meeting of the Labor Committee for Political Action, 11/26/75; correspondence re united efforts of labor movement in electing Carter; COPE activities; Garment Center outdoor rally; letter from Jimmy Carter thanking Chaikin for supporting him as the Democratic nominee and related routine matters.
  - Politics, 1977-1979 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    Chaikin served as Steering Committee Member to Re-elect Daniel P. Moynihan; Robert Abrams campaign for Attorney General; Chaikin, Member of 1977 Inaugural Committee; thank you letters for ILG contributions and related routine matters.
  - Politics, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    Many letters complimenting Chaikin on his nominating speech at the Democratic National Convention; letters of appreciation from politicians; announcements of endorsements for Elizabeth Holtzman, Bess Myerson, and other related routine.
  - Politics, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    Re activities and meeting arrangements of U.S. Senate Democratic Circle; and related routine.
  - Politics, 1982-1983 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    Re related routine political correspondence.
  - Politics, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    Invitation to victory luncheon for the President; master calendar of events for 1984 Democratic National Convention; correspondence from Walter Mondale; several invitations to lunches, etc. during the Democratic Convention and other related routine.
  - Politics. Democratic Party, 1984-1986 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Politics. New York, 1976-1982 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Re support of Gov. Cuomo and Carter-Mondale and related routine.
  - Presidential Classroom for Young Americans, 1980-1986 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - President's Committee on Employment of the Handicapped, 1978-1986 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Press. Morris, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Prodemca, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Professional Air Traffic Controllers Association, 1981-1985 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Re PATCO strike and legal correspondence re White House meetings.
  - Progressive Architecture, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Promotion Fund, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Public Affairs Analysis, Inc., 1984 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    "The Mondale Memoranda" by Joseph Napolitan.
  - Public Agenda Foundation, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Public Art Fund [folder 1 of 2], 1982-1984 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    Re "Garment Worker" sculpture by Judith Weller, includes correspondence re donations and dedication plans.
  - Public Art Fund [folder 2 of 2], 1982-1984 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Public Employees' Relations Association, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Public Forum Productions, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Publication/Media, 1979-1980 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    Correspondence re publications, articles, etc.; correspondence re "60 Minutes" broadcast concerning illegal aliens exploitation and related routine.
  - Publication/Media [folder 1 of 2], 1982-1983 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    Correspondence re articles and radio and television appearances covering Chinese imports, homework, wages and other issues.
  - Publication/Media [folder 2 of 2], 1982-1983 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Publication/Media, 1984-1986 (Box 38, Folder 25)
    Re youth wages, industrial homework and other issues.
  - Puerto Rican Congress of New Jersey, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Puerto Rico, Commonwealth of, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    Re report on economic situation.
  - Puerto Rico. Organizations, 1975-1985 (Box 38, Folder 28)
    Re contributions.
  - Puritan Fashions Corporation, 1982-1985 (Box 38, Folder 29)
    Financial data and correspondence re liquidated damage claims on non-union contractors.
  - Putterman, Violeta (Local 155, Organizer), 1979-1983 (Box 38, Folder 30)
    Correspondence and legal documents re discrimination charge (sex, race and age).
  - Quartet Fashions Inc., 1980-1984 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    Re discharge grievance and other issues.
  - Quirk, Paul, 1977-1979 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    Re election of Secretary-Treasurer of Massachusetts State AFL-CIO.
  - Rainess and Co., 1977 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Ranck, Debra, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Randolph, A. Philip Institute [folder 1 of 3], 1976-1985 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    Re contributions, activities and conferences, conditions of Black Hebrews in Israel and related routine.
  - Randolph, A. Philip Institute [folder 2 of 3], 1976-1985 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Randolph, A. Philip Institute [folder 3 of 3], 1976-1985 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Reader's Digest, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    Re article about organizing efforts of Local 132 by Randy Fitzgerald.
  - Reagan (Ronald) Administration, 1980-1981 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    Invitation to receptions of organized labor and the administration; imports; letter from Chaikin to Reagan expressing his concern with nomination of two individuals to serve on NLRB; from Jackie Presser, Co-Chairman of Presidential Inaugural Committee (1981) requesting Chaikin to participate.
  - Reagan, Ronald, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    Letter thanking Chaikin for his valuable service in his role as Public Member of the U.S. Delegation to the Review Meeting of the Conference on Security and Cooperation in Europe.
  - Recommendations for Employment [folder 1 of 4], 1973-1985 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    Requests for recommendations for employment and college admissions from many individuals.
  - Recommendations for Employment [folder 2 of 4], 1973-1985 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Recommendations for Employment [folder 3 of 4], 1973-1985 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Recommendations for Employment [folder 4 of 4], 1973-1985 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Referrals, 1976-1983 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Refugees, 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    Re Haitian refugees.
  - Regional Plan Association, 1977-1978 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Regrets, 1982-1986 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Reitman, Sidney, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Research and Forecasts,Inc., 1980 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Resumes [folder 1 of 2], 1981-1986 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    Letters and resumes from individuals requesting employment with ILGWU.
  - Resumes [folder 2 of 2], 1981-1986 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Retirees, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    Letters of thanks for pension increase.
  - Reunion of Old Timers, 1976-1986 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Revson Foundation, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Rhode Island AFL-CIO, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Richman, D., 1985 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Richmond Foundation (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Rinker, Alice, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Roll-Back Campaign [folder 1 of 6], 1983-1986 (Box 39, Folder 31)
    Plans and activities re Import Roll-Back Campaign to limit imports. Includes correspondence with many individuals re the import problems and in support of the campaign. clippings, statistical information, releases, editorials, leaflets.
  - Roll-Back Campaign [folder 2 of 6], 1983-1986 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - Roll-Back Campaign [folder 3 of 6], 1983-1986 (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - Roll-Back Campaign [folder 4 of 6], 1983-1986 (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - Roll-Back Campaign [folder 5 of 6], 1983-1986 (Box 39, Folder 35)
  - Roll-Back Campaign [folder 6 of 6], 1983-1986 (Box 39, Folder 36)
  - Roll-Back. Support [folder 1 of 2], 1983 (Box 39, Folder 37)
    Correspondence re interest and support from Congressmen and others.
  - Roll-Back. Support [folder 2 of 2], 1983 (Box 39, Folder 38)
  - Romano, Mary, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 39)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D. Centennial, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 40)
    Leaflets and other related information.
  - Roundabout Theatre Co., 1979 (Box 39, Folder 41)
    Re denial of funding by NYS Council on the Arts.
  - Roussos, Nicholas, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 42)
  - Rudin Management Corporation, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Rural America, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Russ Togs, Inc. [folder 1 of 5], 1980-1985 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    Includes agreements, financial data re use of non-union contractors.
  - Russ Togs, Inc. [folder 2 of 5], 1980-1985 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Russ Togs, Inc. [folder 3 of 5], 1980-1985 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Russ Togs, Inc. [folder 4 of 5], 1980-1985 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Russ Togs, Inc. [folder 5 of 5], 1980-1985 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Rutgers University. Labor Education Center, 1975-1983 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    Correspondence with Norman Eiger, Director of the Center.
  - St. Vincent's Hospital and Medical Center of New York, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    Includes correspondence and proposal re what hospital to provide medical services, as needed, by the Jacob K. Javits Convention Center.
  - Salomon, Haym Foundation, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Sam Landorf, Inc., 1980 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    Re non-union contractors.
  - Santa Clara University of, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Sarachek, Susan, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    Personal correspondence of Mrs. Chaikin.
  - Saucier, Tim, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    Request for personalized photograph of Chaikin.
  - Schmeelk, Richard J., 1978 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Scholarships, 1982-1983 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    Correspondence re ILGWU National Scholarship.
  - Schweiker, Richard S. (Senator), 1973 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Scialo, Adele, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Science and Labor Conference, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Scientists for Orlov and Shcharansky, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    Re human rights in the USSR.
  - Scotty's Fashions, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    Re examination of books by auditors.
  - Securities and Exchange Commission (U.S.), 1984-1985 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Service Employees International Union, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    Re collective bargaining relations at Brandeis University.
  - Seven Springs Center, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    Invitation to participate in symposiums.
  - 75th Anniversary. ILGWU, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    Many letters of congratulations from organizations and individuals; includes suggestions for events; and draft scripts for filming the 35th convention.
  - Shaffer, Joseph (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Shea, William A. (Box 40, Folder 27)
    Re recommendation for Marc Muzur.
  - Shenkar College, 1984-1985 (Box 40, Folder 28)
    (Chaikin, Board of Directors) Related routine.
  - Silverman, Harry, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Slosser, Helen, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Smith, Scott (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Social Democrats, U.S.A., 1975-1983 (Box 40, Folder 32)
    Chaikin, speaker for luncheon honoring Dubinsky and A. Philip Randolph; correspondence regarding the Portugese situation; dinner honoring Chaikin; dinners and receptions honoring many individuals; and other related routine re activities and events.
  - Social Democrats, Young, 1979-1983 (Box 40, Folder 33)
    Re activities and programs; 5 p. "Some Thoughts on John Anderson" by Gus Tyler, ILGWU, Assistant President; 4 p. annual report (1981) of Young Social Democrats and related routine.
  - Social Security Advisory Council, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Social Security. 50th Anniversary, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 35)
    Re celebration.
  - Solidarity, 1980-1985 (Box 40, Folder 36)
    Letters and telegrams protesting arrests of Polish workers.
  - Song, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 37)
    Re labor song composed by ILG member.
  - South African Black Alliance, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 38)
    Publications and speeches by President Mangosuthu G. Buthelezi.
  - South African Trip, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 39)
    Re Labor Desk Study Tour to South Africa.
  - South Bronx Development Office, 1978-1980 (Box 40, Folder 40)
    Re economic development.
  - South Korea, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 41)
    Includes booklet, "Korea, Briefing Paper For President Sol Chaikin"; information re labor dispute at the Dong-IL Textile Co..
  - Soviet Dissidents, 1979-1982 (Box 40, Folder 42)
    Summaries of Sakharov Hearings; papers re formation of a trade union; correspondence re persecution of Soviet workers.
  - Soviet Union, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 43)
    Re oppression of Soviet scientists; 12 p. speech by Chaikin, "Labor in Socialist Societies: Blue Collar Workers in Eastern Europe."
  - Spain, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 44)
  - Speaker's Club, 1981-1982 (Box 40, Folder 45)
    Fund raising activities (correspondence with Thomas P. O'Neill, Speaker, House of Representatives).
  - Special Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 46)
    Papers and article re foreign unions and foreign relations (Israel, Germany, Austria, WFTU, USSR); 4 p. confidential, "memorandum on international situation."
  - Spigner, Archie, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 47)
  - Spitalnick Associates, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 48)
    Re investigation of non-union clothing firm and others by Upper South Department.
  - Springer-Kemp, Maida, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 49)
  - Stanford University, 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 50)
    Correspondence and papers re Conference on the Industrial Working Class in Eastern Europe; 20 p. draft of Chaikin speech; documents about Yugoslavia trade unions; Czechoslovak newsletter; 9 p. speech by Vladimir Budovsky at 3rd Sakharov Hearings; 14 p. paper re Soviet workers; articles re Soviet workers.
  - Starobin, Herman, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 51)
    Re automated sewing system.
  - Stern Fund, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 52)
  - Stewart, Virginia, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 53)
  - Stratford Advisory Group, Inc., 1984-1985 (Box 40, Folder 54)
    Re ILGWU financial/investment matters.
  - Strober, Jacob, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 55)
  - Studds, Gerry E., 1972 (Box 40, Folder 56)
  - Stulberg, Louis, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 57)
    Re luncheon in Stulberg's honor.
  - Sutton, Percy E., 1975 (Box 40, Folder 58)
  - Sweatshops, 1979-1985 (Box 40, Folder 59)
    Re legislative action; letters re editorials and articles.
  - Swedish Textile Workers Union, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 60)
  - Sylbert, Jed, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 61)
  - Sympathy Letters, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 62)
  - Symposium On International Business, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 63)
    Chaikin participated on a panel which discussed current issues in U.S. International Trade and Business (includes 28 p. presentation/speech by Chaikin).
  - Taconic Foundation, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Tan-Jay International Limited, 1984-1986 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    Re Canadian firm accused of failing to bargain collectively in good faith and organizing problems at Tan Jay factory in California.
  - Tannen, Eli S., 1980 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Task Force on Taxation (NYC), 1976 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Tax Legislation, 1979-1981 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Team Optical Manufacturing Corporation, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Teamsters International Union, 1973-1986 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    Includes invitation to Chaikin from President Jackie Presser to attend Teamsters 23rd convention; correspondence re no-raiding and mutual assistance pacts with Presser and Fitzsimmons.
  - Tel Aviv University, 1975-1979 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Telephones, 1983-1985 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    Re ILGWU office telephone systems.
  - Teper, Lazare. Memorial, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    Includes 17 p. statement of Chaikin before the Subcommittee on International Trade, U.S. Senate and other related documents.
  - Textile and Apparel Workers' Unions of Japan-USA, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    85 p. "The Fourth Joint Conference of Textile and....", March 5-7, 1985, N.Y.
  - Textile Caucus, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    (Chaikin, Industry-Labor Panel Member) Includes 25 p. "Proposal, New Patterns of Work, the Humanization of Work Schedules" by Work in America Institute, and other related documents.
  - Textile, Garment and Leather Workers Federation [folder 1 of 2], 1973-1980 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    Includes documents re the 2nd ITGLWF Congress held in Dublin, 1976, and correspondence and related documents concerning other meetings and visits; includes "Report on Health and Safety in the Textile, Garment and Leather Industries," by Sandra Dent, 2nd World Congress, 1976, 24 p.
  - Textile, Garment and Leather Workers Federation [folder 2 of 2], 1973-1980 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Textile Labour Association, 1976-1979 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    Correspondence with A.N. Buch, President inviting Chaikin to visit and thanks for flood relief funds.
  - Textile Workers Union of America, 1971-1973 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Thank-You Letters [folder 1 of 2], 1979-1986 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    Thanks from politicians, consumers, members and others for services, contributions, etc.
  - Thank-You Letters [folder 2 of 2], 1979-1986 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Trade [folder 1 of 3], 1973-1986 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    Re Caribbean trade policy; multi fiber agreement; shoe industry; 22 p. paper by Daniel P. Moynihan, "World Trade and the Wealth of a Nation," June 1984; articles and clippings re trade issues.
  - Trade [folder 2 of 3], 1973-1986 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Trade [folder 3 of 3], 1973-1986 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Trade Adjustment Assistance, 1978-1981 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    Re payment of TAA after exhausting regular unemployment insurance benefits.
  - Trade Imports [folder 1 of 4], 1975-1982 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    Correspondence, articles, clippings, 7 p. discussion paper for AFL-CIO Executive Council Trade Subcommittee, "Memorandum on the Multilateral Trade Negotiations"; Peking Textile negotiations; ABC News-Harris Survey (6 p.) re free trade; U.S. negotiations with Dominican Republic; Administration's Textile Program (includes proposals and correspondence); confidential correspondence from Robert R. Nathan re the inflation spiral and labor (1978); Polish clothing and textile industry; re Federal Trade Commission Report on Imports; imports and the leather industry; 9 p. statement of Dr. Rudolph Oswald, Director, Dept. of Research, AFL-CIO on S.2318, The Buy American Act Amendments, 4/5/78; correspondence with Philip Kochenderfer, President, Icelandic Fashions Corp. re Tariff relief on Icelandic woolen products; South Korea's sweatshops; 68 p. "The Negative Impact of Duty Reductions On the Women's and Children's Apparel Industry and Its Workers" by Chaikin and Lazare Teper; 9 p. "Statement Submitted to the U.S. International Trade Commission In Opposition of Duty Reductions on Articles of Women's and Children's Apparel" by Chaikin, 4/17/75.
  - Trade Imports [folder 2 of 4], 1975-1982 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Trade Imports [folder 3 of 4], 1975-1982 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Trade Imports [folder 4 of 4], 1975-1982 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Trade Imports [folder 1 of 3], 1978-1982 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    Same as previous folders.
  - Trade Imports [folder 2 of 3], 1978-1982 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Trade Imports [folder 3 of 3], 1978-1982 (Box 42, Folder 3)